whackit.co 2019-10-09

# Whack It Games: Privacy Policy

### Cookies

Due to EU regulations for EU visitors to our website we need to obtain your consent to use cookies with your computer.

The cookie files we use are harmless to your computer and but are very important for all websites, we use third party tools and adverts which use cookies for various performance related reasons. These third parties are namely statcounter.com, Google Adsense, various third party advertisers and social media plugins.

If you do not agree with having cookies placed on your computer please exit our website and clear your browser history. Use of our website demonstrates acceptance of our cookie policy.

## We Respect Your Privacy

We know that you care how information about you is used and shared and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. This notice describes the privacy policy of our website. By visiting whackit.co, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

**Controllers of Personal Information**

We do not collect or store any of your personal information when you visit this site.

### No Third Party Sharing of Private Information

We do not share any information with third parties.

whackit.co does not use any cookies.

**Conditions of Use, Notices and Revisions**

If you choose to visit whackit.co, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages and application of internation laws.

### Automatic Information

Examples of the information we view and analyse but do not store include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, connection information such as browser type and version, your operating system and platform, pages you viewed and where you came from to find our site.

**Third party ad's**

Our site uses ad's that are created through google adsense. We do not have control over these ad's and we do not offer any guarantees over the quality of the websites advertising using google adsense. Clicking these ads is at your own risk and visiting any other site is also at your own risk.

### No guarantees

We offer no guarantees regarding the up keep and up time of this website and will not be held liable for any matter relating to our site being down.

We conform with the requirements of Data Protection set by the laws in the North America and the United Kingdom.
